hotelmarketing.com 2015-05-27

# Hotelmarketing.com - must reads for hotel marketers, served fresh daily.

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Hotelmarketing.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.hotelmarketing.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Hotelmarketing.com.

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Hotelmarketing.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: - To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. - To send periodic emails: If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Hotelmarketing.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: Hotelmarketing.com, http://www.hotelmarketing.com / Hotelmarketing'com Wässeri 4 8816 Hirzel Switzerland 079 290 01 84, editor@hotelmarketing.com

This document was last updated on October 27, 2013

Updated daily, Hotelmarketing'com features news and information from around the Web of specific interest to hotel marketers.

Curated from hundreds of sources, highlighting the key takeaways for hotel marketers, our daily must-reads point you to posts we think are worth your time.

Send your press releases, articles or links to interesting news stories to 

**editor'at'hotelmarketing.com**

__Twitter
    @hotelmarketing
__Google+
    +hotelmarketing
RSS
    hotelmarketing.com
